<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days of Recipes</string>

    <string name="day1_title">Classic Margherita Pizza</string>
    <string name="day2_title">Vegetable Stir Fry with Tofu</string>
    <string name="day3_title">Creamy Mushroom Risotto</string>
    <string name="day4_title">Spicy Thai Green Curry</string>
    <string name="day5_title">Homemade Beef Burgers</string>
    <string name="day6_title">Quinoa and Black Bean Salad</string>
    <string name="day7_title">Chicken Alfredo Pasta</string>
    <string name="day8_title">Moroccan Chickpea Stew</string>
    <string name="day9_title">Japanese Ramen with Pork</string>
    <string name="day10_title">Fish Tacos with Mango Salsa</string>
    <string name="day11_title">Butternut Squash Soup</string>
    <string name="day12_title">Greek Salad with Feta Cheese</string>
    <string name="day13_title">Korean Bibimbap</string>
    <string name="day14_title">Spanish Paella</string>
    <string name="day15_title">Maple Glazed Salmon</string>
    <string name="day16_title">Indian Butter Chicken</string>
    <string name="day17_title">Vegan Lentil Dahl</string>
    <string name="day18_title">Shakshuka with Feta</string>
    <string name="day19_title">French Ratatouille</string>
    <string name="day20_title">Mexican Enchiladas</string>
    <string name="day21_title">Beef Stroganoff</string>
    <string name="day22_title">Falafel Wrap with Tzatziki</string>
    <string name="day23_title">New York Style Cheesecake</string>
    <string name="day24_title">Thai Papaya Salad</string>
    <string name="day25_title">Italian Tiramisu</string>
    <string name="day26_title">Cajun Jambalaya</string>
    <string name="day27_title">Turkish Kebabs with Yogurt Sauce</string>
    <string name="day28_title">Chinese Dim Sum Platter</string>
    <string name="day29_title">Portuguese Egg Tarts</string>
    <string name="day30_title">Argentinian Chimichurri Steak</string>

    <string name="day1_ingredients">Pizza dough, mozzarella cheese, tomatoes, basil, olive oil, salt, pepper. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Preheat the oven to 425°F (220°C).\n2. Roll out the pizza dough on a baking sheet.\n3. Spread olive oil on the dough.\n4. Add sliced tomatoes, mozzarella cheese, and basil leaves.\n5. Season with salt and pepper.\n6. Bake for 12-15 minutes or until crust is golden and cheese is bubbly.</string>
    <string name="day2_ingredients">Tofu, bell peppers, carrots, broccoli, soy sauce, sesame oil, ginger. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Press tofu to remove excess moisture, then dice into cubes.\n2. Heat sesame oil in a pan over medium heat.\n3. Add tofu and cook until golden brown.\n4. Add chopped vegetables and ginger, stir-fry for 5-7 minutes.\n5. Pour soy sauce over the mixture and cook for an additional 2 minutes.\n6. Serve hot over rice.</string>
    <string name="day3_ingredients">Arborio rice, mushrooms, vegetable broth, onion, garlic, Parmesan cheese, olive oil. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Heat olive oil in a large saucepan over medium heat.\n2. Add chopped onion and garlic, sauté until fragrant.\n3. Add Arborio rice and stir until lightly toasted.\n4. Gradually add vegetable broth, stirring constantly until absorbed.\n5. Stir in mushrooms and Parmesan cheese.\n6. Cook until the risotto is creamy and the rice is tender.</string>
    <string name="day4_ingredients">Green curry paste, coconut milk, chicken or tofu, bamboo shoots, basil, fish sauce, lime. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Heat green curry paste in a skillet over medium heat.\n2. Add coconut milk and stir until combined.\n3. Add chicken or tofu and cook until almost done.\n4. Stir in bamboo shoots, basil, and fish sauce.\n5. Simmer for 5-7 minutes.\n6. Squeeze lime juice over the curry before serving.</string>
    <string name="day5_ingredients">Ground beef, burger buns, lettuce, tomato, onion, cheese, ketchup, mustard. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Divide ground beef into equal-sized patties and season with salt and pepper.\n2. Heat a skillet or grill over medium-high heat.\n3. Cook patties for 4-5 minutes on each side, or until desired doneness.\n4. Toast burger buns on the grill for 1-2 minutes.\n5. Assemble burgers with lettuce, tomato, onion, cheese, ketchup, and mustard.\n6. Serve immediately.</string>
    <string name="day6_ingredients">Quinoa, black beans, corn, tomatoes, avocado, lime juice, cilantro. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Rinse quinoa under cold water.\n2. In a saucepan, combine quinoa with water and bring to a boil.\n3. Reduce heat, cover, and simmer for 15-20 minutes, or until quinoa is cooked.\n4. In a large bowl, combine cooked quinoa, black beans, corn, diced tomatoes, diced avocado, lime juice, and chopped cilantro.\n5. Season with salt and pepper to taste.\n6. Serve as a salad or side dish.</string>
    <string name="day7_ingredients">Pasta, chicken breast, heavy cream, Parmesan cheese, garlic, butter, parsley. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Cook pasta according to package instructions.\n2. Meanwhile, season chicken breast with salt and pepper.\n3. In a skillet, heat butter over medium heat and cook chicken until golden brown and cooked through.\n4. Remove chicken from skillet and set aside.\n5. In the same skillet, add minced garlic and cook until fragrant.\n6. Stir in heavy cream and Parmesan cheese until sauce is creamy.\n7. Add cooked pasta to the skillet and toss to coat in the sauce.\n8. Slice chicken and serve over pasta, garnished with chopped parsley.</string>
    <string name="day8_ingredients">Chickpeas, tomatoes, onion, garlic, carrots, Moroccan spices, vegetable broth. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Heat olive oil in a large pot over medium heat.\n2. Add diced onion, minced garlic, and sliced carrots, sauté until softened.\n3. Stir in Moroccan spices and cook for 1-2 minutes.\n4. Add chopped tomatoes and cook until softened.\n5. Pour in vegetable broth and chickpeas, bring to a simmer.\n6. Cook for 15-20 minutes, or until vegetables are tender.\n7. Serve hot, garnished with fresh cilantro if desired.</string>
    <string name="day9_ingredients">Ramen noodles, pork belly, broth, soy sauce, mirin, scallions, egg. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Boil eggs in water for 6-7 minutes, then transfer to an ice bath to cool.\n2. In a separate pot, bring broth to a simmer.\n3. Add sliced pork belly and cook until heated through.\n4. Stir in soy sauce and mirin.\n5. Cook ramen noodles according to package instructions.\n6. Assemble ramen bowls with noodles, pork belly, halved boiled egg, and sliced scallions.\n7. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="day10_ingredients">White fish, tortillas, mango, red onion, cilantro, lime, cabbage, avocado. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Season white fish with salt and pepper.\n2. Heat a skillet over medium heat and cook fish until flaky and cooked through.\n3. Meanwhile, warm tortillas in the oven or on the stovetop.\n4. In a bowl, combine diced mango, sliced red onion, chopped cilantro, and lime juice.\n5. Slice avocado and shred cabbage.\n6. Assemble tacos with fish, mango salsa, avocado slices, and shredded cabbage.\n7. Serve with additional lime wedges if desired.</string>
    <string name="day11_ingredients">Butternut squash, onion, vegetable broth, garlic, ginger, cream, olive oil. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).\n2. Peel and dice butternut squash and onion.\n3. Toss with olive oil, minced garlic, and grated ginger.\n4. Roast in the oven for 25-30 minutes, or until squash is tender.\n5. Transfer roasted vegetables to a blender and add vegetable broth.\n6. Blend until smooth.\n7. Pour soup into a pot and stir in cream.\n8. Heat soup over medium heat until warmed through.\n9. Serve hot, garnished with a drizzle of cream and chopped parsley if desired.</string>
    <string name="day12_ingredients">Tomatoes, cucumber, olives, feta cheese, onion, olive oil, lemon juice. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Dice tomatoes, cucumber, and onion.\n2. Pit and slice olives.\n3. In a large bowl, combine tomatoes, cucumber, olives, and diced onion.\n4. Crumble feta cheese over the salad.\n5. Drizzle with olive oil and lemon juice.\n6. Toss to combine.\n7. Serve chilled as a refreshing salad.</string>
    <string name="day13_ingredients">Rice, beef or tofu, assorted vegetables, gochujang, egg, sesame oil, soy sauce. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Cook rice according to package instructions.\n2. In a skillet, heat sesame oil over medium heat.\n3. Add diced beef or tofu and cook until browned.\n4. Add chopped vegetables and stir-fry until tender.\n5. Stir in gochujang and soy sauce.\n6. Push the mixture to one side of the skillet and crack an egg into the empty space.\n7. Scramble the egg and mix it into the rice and vegetables.\n8. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="day14_ingredients">Rice, chicken, shrimp, saffron, bell peppers, peas, onion, chicken broth. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).\n2. Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium heat.\n3. Add diced chicken and cook until browned.\n4. Remove chicken from skillet and set aside.\n5. In the same skillet, cook diced onion and sliced bell peppers until softened.\n6. Stir in rice and cook until lightly toasted.\n7. Add chicken broth, saffron, and peas to the skillet.\n8. Bring to a simmer, then cover and transfer to the oven.\n9. Bake for 20-25 minutes, or until rice is cooked through.\n10. Stir in cooked shrimp and chicken before serving.</string>
    <string name="day15_ingredients">Salmon fillets, maple syrup, soy sauce, garlic, ginger, olive oil. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).\n2. In a small bowl, whisk together maple syrup, soy sauce, minced garlic, grated ginger, and olive oil.\n3. Place salmon fillets on a baking sheet lined with parchment paper.\n4. Brush the maple glaze over the salmon.\n5. Bake for 12-15 minutes, or until salmon is cooked through and flakes easily with a fork.\n6. Serve hot, garnished with chopped green onions if desired.</string>
    <string name="day16_ingredients">Chicken, tomato puree, cream, butter, garam masala, garlic, ginger. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Heat butter in a skillet over medium heat.\n2. Add minced garlic and grated ginger, sauté until fragrant.\n3. Stir in garam masala and cook for 1-2 minutes.\n4. Add tomato puree and cook until thickened.\n5. Add chicken pieces and simmer until cooked through.\n6. Stir in cream and simmer for an additional 5 minutes.\n7. Serve hot, garnished with chopped cilantro if desired.</string>
    <string name="day17_ingredients">Lentils, tomatoes, coconut milk, onion, garlic, ginger, Indian spices. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Rinse lentils under cold water.\n2. In a large pot, heat olive oil over medium heat.\n3. Add diced onion, minced garlic, and grated ginger, sauté until softened.\n4. Stir in Indian spices and cook for 1-2 minutes.\n5. Add diced tomatoes and lentils, stir to combine.\n6. Pour in coconut milk and water.\n7. Bring to a boil, then reduce heat and simmer for 20-25 minutes, or until lentils are tender.\n8. Serve hot, garnished with chopped cilantro if desired.</string>
    <string name="day18_ingredients">Tomatoes, eggs, feta cheese, bell pepper, onion, garlic, cumin, paprika. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).\n2. Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium heat.\n3. Add diced onion, minced garlic, and sliced bell pepper, sauté until softened.\n4. Stir in diced tomatoes, cumin, and paprika.\n5. Make wells in the tomato mixture and crack eggs into the wells.\n6. Crumble feta cheese over the eggs.\n7. Transfer the skillet to the oven and bake for 10-12 minutes, or until eggs are set.\n8. Serve hot, garnished with chopped parsley if desired.</string>
    <string name="day19_ingredients">Zucchini, eggplant, bell peppers, tomatoes, onion, garlic, thyme, olive oil. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).\n2. Slice zucchini, eggplant, bell peppers, and tomatoes.\n3. Arrange the sliced vegetables on a baking sheet.\n4. Drizzle with olive oil and sprinkle with minced garlic and thyme.\n5. Roast in the oven for 20-25 minutes, or until vegetables are tender and slightly caramelized.\n6. Serve hot as a side dish or over cooked quinoa or couscous.</string>
    <string name="day20_ingredients">Tortillas, chicken or beans, enchilada sauce, cheese, onion, garlic, cilantro. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).\n2. In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium heat.\n3. Add diced onion and minced garlic, sauté until softened.\n4. Add shredded cooked chicken or cooked beans and stir to combine.\n5. Warm tortillas in the microwave or on the stovetop.\n6. Spoon a portion of the chicken or bean mixture onto each tortilla.\n7. Roll up tortillas and place seam-side down in a baking dish.\n8. Pour enchilada sauce over the rolled tortillas.\n9. Sprinkle with shredded cheese.\n10. Bake for 20-25 minutes, or until cheese is melted and bubbly.\n11. Serve hot, garnished with chopped cilantro if desired.</string>
    <string name="day21_ingredients">Beef strips, mushrooms, onions, sour cream, beef broth, mustard, garlic. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Heat olive oil in a skillet over medium heat.\n2. Add sliced onions and cook until softened.\n3. Add beef strips and cook until browned on all sides.\n4. Stir in sliced mushrooms and minced garlic.\n5. Pour in beef broth and bring to a simmer.\n6. Stir in mustard and simmer for 5-7 minutes.\n7. Remove from heat and stir in sour cream.\n8. Serve hot over cooked egg noodles or mashed potatoes.</string>
    <string name="day22_ingredients">Chickpeas, garlic, herbs, tortilla, yogurt, cucumber, garlic, lemon. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Drain and rinse chickpeas under cold water.\n2. In a food processor, combine chickpeas, minced garlic, chopped herbs, and lemon juice.\n3. Pulse until mixture is coarsely chopped.\n4. Spread chickpea mixture onto tortillas.\n5. In a bowl, combine yogurt, minced garlic, and lemon juice.\n6. Thinly slice cucumber.\n7. Spread yogurt mixture over chickpea mixture on tortillas.\n8. Top with sliced cucumber.\n9. Roll up tortillas and serve as wraps or cut into pinwheels.</string>
    <string name="day23_ingredients">Cream cheese, graham crackers, sugar, eggs, vanilla extract, sour cream. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Preheat the oven to 325°F (160°C).\n2. Crush graham crackers into fine crumbs.\n3. In a bowl, mix together graham cracker crumbs, sugar, and melted butter.\n4. Press the mixture into the bottom of a springform pan to form the crust.\n5. In a large bowl, beat cream cheese until smooth.\n6. Add sugar, eggs, vanilla extract, and sour cream, and beat until well combined.\n7. Pour the cream cheese mixture over the crust in the pan.\n8. Bake for 45-50 minutes, or until the center is set.\n9. Allow cheesecake to cool completely before serving.</string>
    <string name="day24_ingredients">Green papaya, tomatoes, green beans, peanuts, lime juice, fish sauce, garlic. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Peel and shred green papaya.\n2. Slice tomatoes and trim green beans.\n3. Crush peanuts into coarse pieces.\n4. In a large bowl, combine shredded papaya, sliced tomatoes, trimmed green beans, and crushed peanuts.\n5. In a small bowl, mix together lime juice, fish sauce, minced garlic, and sugar.\n6. Pour dressing over the salad and toss to combine.\n7. Serve chilled as a refreshing salad or side dish.</string>
    <string name="day25_ingredients">Ladyfingers, espresso, mascarpone cheese, cocoa powder, sugar, eggs, rum or brandy. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Brew espresso and allow it to cool.\n2. In a bowl, beat together mascarpone cheese, sugar, and egg yolks until smooth.\n3. In a separate bowl, beat egg whites until stiff peaks form.\n4. Gently fold the beaten egg whites into the mascarpone mixture.\n5. Dip ladyfingers into cooled espresso and layer them in a serving dish.\n6. Spread half of the mascarpone mixture over the ladyfingers.\n7. Repeat layers with remaining ladyfingers and mascarpone mixture.\n8. Dust the top with cocoa powder.\n9. Chill in the refrigerator for at least 4 hours or overnight.\n10. Serve chilled, garnished with shaved chocolate if desired.</string>
    <string name="day26_ingredients">Rice, chicken, shrimp, andouille sausage, bell peppers, onion, Cajun seasoning. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Cook rice according to package instructions.\n2. Meanwhile, heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium heat.\n3. Add diced chicken, sliced andouille sausage, and sliced bell peppers, sauté until chicken is cooked through.\n4. Add peeled and deveined shrimp to the skillet and cook until pink and opaque.\n5. Stir in Cajun seasoning to taste.\n6. Serve the chicken, sausage, shrimp, and peppers over cooked rice.</string>
    <string name="day27_ingredients">Lamb or beef, yogurt, garlic, tomatoes, bell peppers, onions, spices. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium heat.\n2. Add diced onions and cook until softened.\n3. Add diced lamb or beef and cook until browned.\n4. Stir in minced garlic and cook until fragrant.\n5. Add diced tomatoes and sliced bell peppers to the skillet.\n6. Season with spices of your choice (such as cumin, coriander, paprika, and cinnamon).\n7. Simmer until the meat is tender and the sauce is thickened.\n8. Serve hot, garnished with a dollop of yogurt.</string>
    <string name="day28_ingredients">Variety of fillings (shrimp, pork, vegetables), dumpling wrappers, soy sauce, sesame oil. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Prepare your desired fillings, such as chopped shrimp, cooked pork, and diced vegetables.\n2. Place a small spoonful of filling in the center of each dumpling wrapper.\n3. Moisten the edges of the wrapper with water and fold in half, pressing to seal.\n4. Heat oil in a skillet over medium heat.\n5. Place dumplings in the skillet and cook until golden brown on the bottom.\n6. Add water to the skillet and cover, steaming the dumplings until cooked through.\n7. Serve hot with soy sauce and sesame oil for dipping.</string>
    <string name="day29_ingredients">Puff pastry, eggs, sugar, cream, vanilla extract, lemon zest. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).\n2. Roll out puff pastry and cut into squares.\n3. Place a spoonful of filling in the center of each square.\n4. Beat together eggs, sugar, cream, vanilla extract, and lemon zest.\n5. Brush the edges of the pastry squares with the egg mixture.\n6. Fold the pastry squares in half to form triangles and press to seal.\n7. Place turnovers on a baking sheet lined with parchment paper.\n8. Brush the tops with the remaining egg mixture.\n9. Bake for 15-20 minutes, or until golden brown and puffed.\n10. Serve warm or at room temperature.</string>
    <string name="day30_ingredients">Steak, parsley, garlic, olive oil, red wine vinegar, red pepper flakes. \n\nInstructions:\n1. Season the steak with salt, pepper, and red pepper flakes.\n2. Heat olive oil in a skillet over medium-high heat.\n3. Add minced garlic and cook until fragrant.\n4. Add the steak and sear on both sides until desired doneness.\n5. Remove the steak from the skillet and let it rest for a few minutes.\n6. Drizzle with red wine vinegar and garnish with chopped parsley before serving.</string>


</resources>